export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Which of the following statements are true ?',
        choices: ['Node.js is a server-side language', 'Node.js is a client-side language', 'Node.js is both server and client side language', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'Node.js is a server-side language',
      },
      {
        question: '_____ is an interactive shell that processes Node.',
        choices: ['REPL', 'REAL', 'RESP', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'REPL',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the full form of REPL ?',
        choices: ['Read Eval Print Loop', 'Research Eval Print Learn', 'Read Earn Point Loop', 'Read Eval Point Loop'],
        type: 'MCQ', 
        correctAnswer: 'Read Eval Print Loop',
      },
      {
        question: 'Node.js is written in which language ?',
        choices: ['C++', 'JavaScript', 'C', 'Java'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'JavaScript',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can we install the node body-parser module ?',
        choices: ['npm install body-parser', 'node install body-parser', 'node.js install body-parser', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'npm install body-parser',
      },      
      {
        question: 'Which of the following are examples of node modules ?',
        choices: ['Express', 'Body-parser', 'Soket.io', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },      
      {
        question: 'To include the HTTP server in the node module, what function do we use ?',
        choices: ['get()', 'require()', 'createServer()','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'require()',
      },      
      {
        question: 'How can we expose node modules ?',
        choices: ['exports', 'expose', 'requires', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'exports',
      },
      {
        question: 'What method is used to return the current working directory of the process ?',
        choices: ['cwd()', 'pwd()', 'cmd()', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'cwd()',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Default scope in Node.js application is ?',
        choices: ['Global', 'Local', 'Local to Global', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'Local',
      },  
      {
        question: 'How can we initiate a NodeJS file called Hello in Node ?',
        choices: ['Hello.js', 'node Hello.js', 'javascript Hello.js', 'node Hello'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'node Hello.js',
      },  
      {
        question: 'The advantages of using node modules are ?',
        choices: ['Provides a means of dividing up tasks', 'Provides a means of reuse of program code', 'Provides a means of testing individual parts of the program', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which of the following statements are true: 1.NodeJS is multithreaded. 2. The Buffer class is a global class that can be accessed without importing a buffer module.',
        choices: ['Both true', 'Both false', '1 true and 2 false','1 false and 2 true'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: '1 false and 2 true',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which of the following is a valid HTTP method ?',
        choices: ['GET', 'PUT', 'POST', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which of the following fs module is used to close a file ?',
        choices: ['fs.close()', 'fs.closeFile()', 'fs.closePath()', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'fs.close()',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which of the following NodeJS module splits up a web address into readable parts ?',
        choices: ['Express', 'Cors', 'URL', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'URL',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which of the following NodeJS modules is used for file uploads ?',
        choices: ['formidable', 'fs', 'express', 'files'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'formidable',
      },  
      {
        question: 'Which node module is used to serve static resources in NodeJS ?',
        choices: ['static', 'non-static', 'http', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'non-static',
      },  
      {
        question: '_____ is a software service that allows 2 or more applications to talk to each other ?',
        choices: ['REST', 'API', 'Both A and B','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'API',
      },  
      {
        question: 'What is a callback ?',
        choices: ['The callback is a technique in which a method calls back the caller method', 'The callback is an asynchronous equivalent for a function', 'Both A and B','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQ',
        correctAnswer: 'The callback is an asynchronous equivalent for a function',
      },  
    ],
  };
  